Hello friends welcome to my YouTube channel
friends today we will talk about target pricing of pomegranate
construction site Rail India
ICICI Lombard General Insurance and
friends Bandhan Bank Can Tech Mahindra
shares so friends let's
start the video friends if you also
want to open your demat account then the link
is given in the description box you can open your demat account by clicking on that link you
can subscribe to any or any share this
friends like the video subscribe to the channel
friends first of all we
will talk about these construction so friends
construction with my
friends
subscribe money friends there is
273 20 paise in construction then
we will talk about Rail Scindia so
friends ICICIdirect has
given a reduced rating on Rail India friends
target price is 235 that friends
friends opening method of India is 253
its closing method is 238 40 paise high
price is 253 friends friends
India closing is 242 rupees and with
money friends now we will talk about ICICI
Lombard General Insurance so friends
Share Khan has
given his bike rating on ICICI Lombard General Insurance,
friends the target price is 1620,
friends ICICI Lombard General
Insurance opened at 1315 above,
its low price was fixed at 1280 rupees, high price
of 1327 rupees, friends ICICI
Lombard General Insurance closed at
1300 rupees 5 and 75 paise, friends now
we will talk about Bandhan Bank, friends
HDFC Securities has
given its bike rating on Bandhan Bank, friends the target
price is 400 rupees 5, friends the
opening method of Bandhan Bank is
326.50 paise, its low price is 30 paise,
price is 33500 paise, friends the number of Bandhan Bank is
332.75, friends in such a situation
friends
1850 friends appointed 295 low price
1262 paise
1297 paise friends
1200 ₹70
friends
appointed you subscribe to our channel,
like the video, thanks for watching.